Kimberly Brannian

Professional Summary

An adept, self-starter with more than 10 years as an independent hairstylist who built a loyal clientele based on empathy, listening and delivering outstanding service. Determined and creative with a vast array of work and life experience, love taking on new challenges and learning new skills. Looking for a place to grow and flourish while offering high value.

Work History

Self Employed - Hairstylist

Portland, OR

02/2013 - Current

 Created memorable client experiences with a mix of true professionalism, good humor, empathy, listening and ability to remember all of the little details learned over the years

Boa - Host

City Of Los Angeles, CA

04/2009 - 04/2010

 Governed dining area with natural leadership talents and organizational strategies focused on balancing guest and business needs.

Geranium Lake Flowers - Office Manager

Portland, OR

06/2006 - 06/2008

- Coordinated special projects and managed schedules
- Maintained back-end of online store

Liberty Capital - Office Manager

Portland, OR

10/2001 - 06/2006

Managed office operations

- ➤ brannian@gmail.com
- 5035778815
- Portland, OR 97203

Skills

- Outstanding Client Retention
- Customer consultation
- Detail-orientated
- Strong leader

Education

04/2022

Epicodus

Portland, OR

Current Student: Web Development

01/2011

Aveda Institute Portland

Portland, OR

Hair Design

06/2005

Portland State University

Portland, OR

Bachelors Of Art: Marketing